Poland refused the passage of Soviet troops
Польша отказала проходе советских войск
where through its territory And where
куда через её территорию А куда
Soviet troops should have
советские войска должны были
passed And in support of
пройти А в поддержку
Serbia what Serbia
Сербии какой Сербии
Swa
Сва
Czechoslovakia
Чехословакия
Hello Hello, I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk and you are from Russia Siberia
Хмельницк и вы откуда Россия Сибирь
Tomsk
Томск
Tomsk Got it Question for you to Tomsk How do you
Томск Понял Вопрос к вам к Томску Как вы
feel about such an organization as
относитесь к такой организации как
NATO is absolutely calm. Do you know how
НАТО абсолютно спокойно А знаете как
NATO stands for North Atlantic Alliance? I understand,
НАТО Северно Атлантический Альянс
if you translate North
Поня если перевести там Норд
Atlantic there, why why are the Russians so much
Атлантик А почему почему россияне так бо
NATO?
НАТО
Created to
очередь Создана для
confront the Soviet Union,
противостояния Советскому Союзу
initially in the future
изначально в дальнейшем
Russia Well, this is because the
России Ну так это ж из-за того что
Soviet Union attacked other countries
Советский Союз нападал на другие страны
A  why did they decide so yes the Soviet Union
А с чего так решили да Советский Союз
captured Czechoslovakia Poland Hungary and the
захватил Чехословакию Польшу Венгрию и
GDR In what year was it in forty-
ГДР В каком году это было в сорок
fifth in forty-five after the
Пятом в сорок пятом после того как
Soviet Union won
Советский Союз выиграл
with the
при
support of Great Britain and the United
поддержке Великобритании и Соединённых
States of America won Germany a little
Штатов Америки выиграл Германию немножко
wrong not the Soviet Union with the support of
не так не Советский Союз при поддержке
the States and Britain  and the states of Britain and the
Штатов и Британии а штаты Британия и
Soviet Union as the Anti-Hitler
Советский Союз как Антигитлеровская
Coalition Yes,
коалиция Да
it won, it won this war Yes, the question is
выиграла выиграла эту войну Да вопрос
why why Soviet troops Yes, they
почему почему советские войска Да
remained standing in Poland in Czechoslovakia
остались стоять в Польше в Чехословакии
and they captured these
да и захватили эти
states, firstly, don’t put the
государства вы во-первых не ставьте
question on its head
вопрос с ног на голову
initially, and secondly, in the sense  what
изначально а во-вторых в смысле что
why question What did Soviet troops do after the victory
почему вопрос Что делали после победы
over Germany in
над Германией советские войска в
Czechoslovakia in Poland Yes
Чехословакии в Польше Да
in
в
Hungary Please tell me Germany
Венгрии Скажите пожалуйста Германия
Czech Republic Poland fought against the Soviet
Чехия Польша воевали против Советского
Union Which included
Союза В который входила в том числе
Ukraine, I understood Poland, for example, did not fight
Украина понял Польша например не воевала
against the Soviet Union, but the Soviet Union
против Советского Союза а Советский Союз
fought against Poland together with  by fascist
против Польши воевал вместе с фашистской
Germany, the Soviet Union dismembered
Германией Советский Союз расчленил
Poland and captured part of its territories. And
Польшу и захватил часть её территорий А
why did this
почему это
happen because the Soviet Union of
произошло потому что Советский Союз
Nazi Germany signed the
нацистской Германии подписали пакт
Molotov Trail Pact as allies because of the
Молотова тропа как союзники потому
refusal to allow Soviet troops to pass during
отказа в проходе советских войск при
aggression, once again Poland refused the passage of
агрессии ещ раз Польша отказала проходе
Soviet troops where through its territory
советских войск куда через её территорию
And where are the Soviet troops  should have
А куда советские войска должны были
passed in support of
пройти в поддержку
Serbia, which
Сербии какой
Serbia Czechoslovakia once again Serbia
Серби Чехословакия е раз Серби
Czechoslovakia On September 1,
чехословаки 1 сентября тридцать девятого
1939, Hitler's Germany attacks
года гитлеровская Германия нападает на
Poland and the Soviet Union, as an ally of
Польшу и Советский Союз как союзник
Hitler's Germany, also attacks
гитлеровской Германии тоже нападает на
Poland, takes it in half, they took
Польшу забирает себе пополам они забрали
Poland
Польшу
and the
а Суть в чём
point was, you never
заключалась Вот вы никогда не
thought  Why did
задумывались Почему
Churchill call Poland a hyena and
Черчиль обозвал Польшу гиеной а
never thought about it, but Poland is a
никогда не задумывался но Польша
sovereign state Why did the
суверенное государство Для чего
Soviet Union, together with Nazi
Советский Союз вместе с нацистской
Germany and Hitler Yes, dismember Poland, I
германи с Гитлером Да расчленили Польшу
think and I think a lot will become
думаю и я думаю вам очень многое станет
clear to you. Let's
понятное Давайте
tell Poland
расскажите Польша
first of all how many times
во-первых её сколько раз
as
в
a result after the First World War  Do
результате после Первой мировой войны
n’t you think at whose whim it was
вам не кажется по чьей прихоти она была
united? I have no idea. The thing is,
объединена Понятия не имею вот Дело в
look, Hitler
том что смотрите как раз Гитлер та же
says the same thing: why, as a result of the
самое говорит что почему в результате
First World War, some kind of
первой мировой войны какая-то
Czechoslovakia appeared, some kind of all these
Чехословакия появилась какая-то всё вот
countries were all according to someone else
такие страны были всё по чьей-то прихоти
they
не по чьей-то они состоящие
were geopolitical entities on a whim, and why
геополитические сущности были да почему
in 1939 the Soviet Union
в тридцать девятом году Советский Союз
attacked Poland along with the Nazis, everything is
напал на Польше вместе с нацистами всё
everything. Here you are, you are just an extreme, very
всё Вот вы вот вы просто крайний очень
uninteresting, uneducated person, and that
неинтересный необразованный человек а то
is, you will now run away; you have no answer
есть вы сейчас убежит у вас нету ответа
to the question why  The Soviet Union attacked
на вопрос почему Советский Союз напал на
Poland, you will cut it off that I am an uninteresting,
Польша вы срежем что я неинтересный
uneducated person and will run away, I
необразованный человек и убежит я
understand correctly, the simple thing is that
правильно понимаю просто дело в том что
I will not run away, I will explain it to me, I want, I want to,
я не Убегу я гда обясните мне я хочу я
I’m not going to explain to you, you are
хочу по я вам не собираюсь объяснять вы
generally an educated, literate person, I
вообще образованный грамотный человек я
want to really figure it out Can you  If
хочу реально разобраться Можете вы Если
you really understand You are
вы действительно понимаете Вы же более
smarter, more educated Yes Explain
умный более образованный Да Объясните
why the Soviet Union attacked Poland
почему Советский Союз напал на Польшу не
I don’t I don’t know Is this how an educated,
имею Я не знаю А разве так образованный
literate person can answer, I
грамотный человек может ответить вот я
don’t know, I’m a literate person and says I
не знаю я грамотный человек и говорит я
don’t know something, tell me, great
не знаю чего-то расскажи мне великий
teacher  Guru Yes, who am I talking to now
учитель Гуру Да что я с кем сейчас
with an educated literate
общаюсь с образованным грамотным
person or with someone who
человеком или с тем который ничего не
knows nothing if you don’t know anything
знает если вы ничего не знаете
at least the basics Study history Well, here’s the
хотя бы основы Изучите истории Ну вот
basis of history, what was it in the
основа истории что Что такое было в
basics of history that the Soviet Union, as
основах истории что Советский Союз как
an ally of the Nazis, Hitler Yes, attacked  They
союзник нацистов Гитлера Да напал на
weighed Poland against the background of
Польшу на весили себе там на фоне
the Cross and are trying to rub something into someone,
Крестик и пытаетесь кому-то что-то
but you understand with your
втереть но понимаете вот с вашим
rubbing in. With such an approach that I
втиранием С таким подходом что я этого
don’t know this, this is a fact, I don’t know that, I do
не знаю это факт я не знаю того я тоже
n’t know either, this is crazy
не знаю это лупень
how I see my education so far  that
зна Как я вижу моё образование пока что
Hitler and the Soviet Union
Гитлер вместе с советским союзом
concluded the Molotov Pact for the division of
заключили пакт Молотова ринт разделе
influence in Europe, that is, the Soviet Union
влияния в Европе то есть Советский Союз
as and as an ally of Hitler Yes, it attacked
как и как союзник Гитлера Да напал на
Poland, that’s education, you
Польшу вот образованието хотя бы
need to have at least a little Yes, but I have a
маленько надо иметь Да но я у меня есть
history education Kiev
историческое образование Киевский
National Taras
национальный университет имени Тараса
Shevchenko University Faculty of History  I
Шевченко исторический факультет У меня
have and who by
есть а кто по образовани
education have 18 years of
образование вот у меня 18 лет
historical practice, in 2 years I will be
исторической практики через 2 года будет
based on you know, if we
основывается знаете если мы будем
talk about a topic on
разговаривать на тему на которую я в
which I am an expert, I am afraid that
которой я являюсь специалист Я боюсь что
you will simply
вы просто
blow me away, I am not an expert in history But
сдует я не специалист в истории Но тем
nevertheless  less I seem to know her better than you,
не менее я её по Похоже лучше вас
let’s talk about
знаю давайте давайте поговорим тогда на
my topic then. Don’t let us finish with this topic first.
мою тему Не давайте мы сначала с этой
You’re interested in you, it’s just that
темой закончим вас интересует вы просто
you started this topic, you started
это же вы начали эту тему вы начали
talking. It’s not me who said. You said
говорить Это же не я сказал Вы сказали
that Poland did not allow passage there to
что Польша не дала проходу там к
Somehow I didn’t understand Yugoslavia to Serbia
Югославии к Сербии какой-то не понял
at all I was educated My education
вообще я был образован моё образование
Tomsk University of
Томский университет управления
Radioelectronics Management So you want to talk about this
Радиоэлектроники Вот вы хотите на эту
topic No I don’t want to I
тему пообщаться Нет не хочу Я хочу
still want to talk about Poland and the Soviet
вс-таки на тему Польши и Советского
Union to close the question
Союза закрыть вопрос
so you
так-то
float Well look at me how  techie
плаваете Да вот смотрите мне как технарь
Tell me, you say that the Soviet
Расскажите Вот вы говорите что Советский
Union attacked Poland because Poland did
Союз напал на Польшу потому что Польша
not allow troops to enter Serbia. So you
не дала проход войск в сербию Так вы уже
yourself are starting to invent and contradict
сами начинаете придумывать и перечить
my words. The Soviet Union attacked Poland
мои слова Советский Союз напал на Польшу
no Germany Germany attacked Poland
нет Германия Германия напала на Поль
correctly and the troops of the Soviet Union
правильно и войска Советского Союза
ended up on the territory of
оказались на территории
Poland  turned out turned out to be That's But why
Польши оказались оказались Вот Но почему
turned out to be Why But here I am I'm a
оказались Почему А вот вот Я вот Вас Я
techie I'm not in this Yes look Yes
технарь Я в этом не Да смотрите Да
the question I, as a historian, ask the
вопрос я как историк спрашиваю власти
Polish authorities did not invite the troops of the Soviet
Польши не приглашали войска Советского
Union to their
Союза на свою
territory in your opinion in order to fight with
территорию по-вашему чтобы по воевать с
some third country  you need
с какой-то третьей страной нужно
an invitation if you want to send
приглашение если вы хотите ээ ввести
troops into the territory of a foreign state
войска на территорию чужого государства
Yes, you need an invitation or permission from the
Да Вам нужно приглашение или разрешение
authorities of that state. If you
властей этого государства Если Вы
enter without permission, it’s
заходите своими возми без разрешения это
called Intervention, invasion,
называется Интервенция вторжение
occupation. Listen, you remind me of a really
оккупация Слушайте вот вы мне
naive boy. Yes, very naive
наивного мальчика Да очень наивные
boys.  That’s the truth I’m looking at you and I’m not
мальчики Вот правда Я вот смотрю на вас
funny I’m a
имне смешно
man with the intelligence of a boy Yes
собой мужчину с интеллектом мальчика Да
I’m a man with the intelligence of a boy
я вот мужчина с интеллектом мальчика
Look I’m looking at the facts The Soviet Union
смотрите я смотрю факты Советский Союз
took and led its troops into the territory of
взял вёл свои войска на территорию
Poland Yes he took Polish prisoners of war
Польши Да взял польских военнопленных
for some reason Yes whom he later shot at
почему-то Да которых потом расстрелял в
Katyn Yes he spent together  there was a parade with the Germans
катыни Да провёл вместе с немцами парад
in Brest Yes and uh the Germans Yes by agreement
в Бресте Да и ээ немцы Да по соглашению
they handed over Brest to the Soviet Union it was
передали Брест Советскому Союзу было
like this
такое
Repeat
Повторите
please I repeat see somehow the
пожалуйста повторяю смотрите как-то
troops of the Soviet Union ended up on
войска Советского Союза оказались на
Polish territory they captured Polish
территории Польши захватили польских
prisoners of war who were then shot
военнопленных которых потом расстреляли
at Katyn Yes somehow Brest
в катыни Да как-то Брест в Бресте
held a joint parade in Brest  with the Nazis and the
провели совместный парад с нацистами и
Nazis solemnly handed over Brest to
нацисты торжественно передали Брест
the Soviet Union how did it happen in
Советскому Союзу как так получилось в
what year I’ll clarify again
каком году я ещё раз Уточняю
939 in the year thirty-nine yes Okay
939 в тридцать девятом году да Хорошо
Let’s figure it out With the year thirty-nine
Давайте разберёмся С тридцать девятым
Let’s September 1, thirty-nine
Давайте 1 сентября тридцать девятого
what
года что там
happened there Hitler a Nazi ally of the
произошло Гитлер нацист союзник
Soviet Union attacked
Советского Союза напал на
Poland is
Польшу вот
great. Why did he attack it
отлично А почему он на неё напал потому
because he is an aggressor because the aggressor doesn’t
что он агрессор потому что агрессору не
need a reason, he wanted and attacked like
нужно причина он захотел и напал как
Putin there because he thinks that
Путин там потому что он считает что вот
he needs land, he needs living
ему нужно земли ему нужно жизненное
space for the
пространство для
Germans, you’ve been screwed, you’ve been screwed because
германской понесло вас понесло вас
emotions prevail because  what I
поне эмоции превалируют потому что я
understand is how the
понимаю как гитр го
German army needs living space
германской нужно жизненное пространство
to the east attacked Poland you understand
на восток напал на Польшу понимаете Вы
like Hitler I mean you understand Hitler
как Гитлер понимаете То есть вы Гитлер
I taught I am a historian by
понимаете Я учил я историк по
training we taught it all yes it doesn’t
образованию мы учили это всё да неважно
matter
неважно
[laughter]
[смех]
yes
да
oh the hollow yes
ох полых дах
me why the Soviet Union was captured  part of
мне почему Советский Союз захватил часть
Poland together with Nazi Germany
Польши вместе с нацистской Германией
unleashed the First World War the Second World
развязав Первую мировую Вторую Мировую
War after all Wait a minute
Войну всё-таки Подождите а хорошо 1
September 1st You said the
сентября Вот вы сказали тридцать
Second World War began in thirty-nine Yes and the Great
началась Вторая мировая Да а Великая
Patriotic War when the Great
Отечественная когда началась великая
Patriotic War began there is no such war this is
отечественная нету такой войны это
an invention of Soviet propaganda
выдумка Советской пропаганды
[music]
[музыка]
Well let it be  so, well, this is a rotten
Хорошо пусть будет так ну это это гнилая
excuse,
отмазка
I know, against the Soviet Union. When did
знаю на Советский Союз Когда произошло
the attack take place,
нападение
uh, Hitler's Germany as an ally of the
ээ гитлеровская Германия как союзник
Soviet Union Yes, it treacherously attacked the
Советского Союза Да напала вероломно на
Soviet Union, violating the Molotov Treaty,
Советский Союз нарушив договор Молотова
rebet propa on June 22,
ребет пропа 22 июня
1941, that's the difference of 2 years in
1941 года вот разница в 2 года в года
these 2 years, the Soviet Union as an ally of the
эти 2 года Советский Союз как союзник
Nazis  Germany while the whole world
нацистской Германии пока весь мир
was fighting the Nazis Yes, the Soviet Union
боролся с нацистами Да Советский Союз
supplied Germany with steel, coal, and
поставлял в Германию сталь уголь
wood Yes, it helped with the military intervention
древесину Да помогал военной интервенцию
in Poland, yes, it captured the Baltic countries,
в Польше да да захватил страны балтии
Latvia, Lithuania, Estonia,
Латвию Литву Эстонию
yes, and where are some facts? You just
да А где какие-то факты Вот вы просто
say so,
вот чисто так
yes, open the facts and see, Yes,
Да факты открывайте и смотрите Да
trade  connections of the Soviet Union with
торговые связи Советского Союза с
Nazi Germany three de soro soro
нацистской Германией три де соро соро
per year yes open the takeover
пер год есть да открываете захват
Soviet
Советская
occupation of Lithuania Latvia Estonia
оккупация Литвы Латвии Эстонии
fact there were connections but there were some connections
факт были были связи но связи были какие
and illegible connections there were inconstant
а неразборчивые связи были непостоянные
connections there were dubious connections stop
связи были сомнительные связи перестань
behaving like a Clone Come on, come on, I
себя вести как Клон Ну давай давай ну я
want it  hear vki you 10 minutes you
же хочу услышать вки ты 10 минут ты 10
try to squeeze out some kind of answer from yourself for 10 minutes
минут пробуешь выдавить из себя какой-то
but there is no answer why the Soviet Union
ответ а ответа нет почему Советский Союз
attacked Poland Don’t act like a clown
напал на Польшу Не веди себя как клоун А
Why the Soviet Union when you have no
почему Советский Союз когда у тебя нет
arguments you will be a clown not a clown I
аргументов ты будешь клоун не клоун я
will
тебя буду
put pressure on you The
дожимает
Union attacked
Союз напал на
Poland was attacked by the Soviet Union, let's immediately
Польшу Советский Союз давай так сразу
agree,
договоримся
the question was what is the name of this
нападал вопрос как называется этот
process that the Soviet Union did with
процесс который сделал Советский Союз с
Poland, there was no process. Well,
Польшей процесса никакого не было Э ну
there was a process of moving the troops of the Soviet
был процесс перемещения войск Советского
Union to the territory of Poland, capturing
Союза на территорию Польши захват там
prisoners of war there and establishing their
военнопленных и установление своей
power behind the fence, annexing their
власти за забор аннексировать себе
territories. What was the name of this  a
территории Как назывался этот
process, if not
процесс если не
an attack, this is a process Well,
нападение это этот процесс Ну давай
then reformulate it differently, yes, yes,
тогда переформулируйте по-другому да да
come on
давай
And these Polish lands
А эти земли польские кому
were given to the Soviet
отошли Советскому
Union And in the future, Well, Belarus, Ukraine are
Союзу А в дальнейшем Ну Беларусь Украина
different Yes,
разные Да
and Russia got something
и России что-то досталось
mm Kaliningrad
мм Калининградская
region Kaliningrad region is
область Калининградская область - это
Poland
Польша
or maybe  Germany was Poland KRG
а может быть Германия была Польша крг
was Poland no The Queen before this
была Польша нет Королеве до этого
was Krolevets yes it’s shorter so
кролевец был да это короче так вот
forever let it be Germany Russia
вовеки давай это была Германия России
nothing went away what’s next
ничего не отошло что дальше
That’s what’s next So after all, Poland then
Вот что дальше Так всё-таки Польше тогда
needs to demand indemnity from Ukraine The thing is,
надо требовать контрибуцию с укра Дело в
look, there are the Helsinki
том что смотрите есть хельсинские
agreements  the seventy-fifth year of the
соглашения семьдесят пятого года
seventies, yes, about the unchanged
семидесятых годах да о неизменен
state of Europe in replacing claims Yes,
государства Европе в замены претензий Да
no one is demanding from anyone Yes, so
никто от кого не требует Да так вот
the question is what Poland needs, Poland will tell us
вопрос что нужно Польше скажет нам
what we need from Poland, we will tell
Польша что нужно нам от Польши мы скажем
Poland, you answer Why did the Soviet Union
Польше вы ответьте Зачем Советский Союз
attack Poland If you say it didn’t
напал на Польшу Если вы говорите не
attack  So what did he do you run away
напал Так что он сделал ты убегаешь
again Let us rephrase if he didn’t
снова Давай мы перефрази если он не
attack Poland what he did Soviet
напал на Польшу что он сделал Советский
Union The Soviet Union included at
Союз Советский Союз в него входила как
least Russia and Ukraine yes yes Russia
минимум Россия и Украина да да Россия
Ukraine Belarus everything Yes why did we all
Украина Белорусь всё Да зачем мы все
Russia Ukraine and Belarus attack
Россия Украина и Белорусь напали на
Poland at thirty  ninth year Explain to
Польшу в тридцать девятом году Объясни
me that yes and
мне вот да и
and the essence of what is Well, finally, the essence
и Суть в чём заключается Ну наконец Суть
of what is why they attacked is
в чём Зачем напали в том заключается
that Ukraine needs to return Lviv to the Yes,
что Украине надо Львов вернуть в по Да
we will return Lviv to the Poles, you explain
мы мы вернём Львов полякам ты объясни
why then we are Ukrainians,
зачем тогда мы вместе с вами украинцы
Belarusians, and the Russians attacked Poland  for
белорусы И россияне напали на Польшу за
helping Hitler Why return it
помогли Гитлеру Зачем возвращай
back we Yes we will return we with Poland
возвращай мы Да мы вернём мы с Польшей
we will agree in short yes with them we will return them to us they will return it
мы договоримся короче да с ними мы им
to us In short everything is fine You
вернём они нам Короче всё нормально Ты
tell me why we attacked in
расскажи мне зачем мы тогда напали в
1939 Tom anecdote of a
тридцать девятом году Том анекдоте
tomato cut yes yes Super look we
отцепа от помидоры да да Супер смотри мы
we to the Poles  we'll give it back to the lion, we tell them,
мы полякам отдадим львом мы им говорим
take the lion, they say, We don't want to pay you pensions from the European Union,
вам платить пенсии евросоюзом возьмём
we'll take yours, we've been telling the Poles for 10 years already, in 14
ваш мы говорим полякам уже 10 лет за 14
years and 88 days we've been saying Take Lviv, they
лет и 88 дней говорим Заберите Львов они
say so, now tell me why we
говорят так ты мне теперь скажи зачем мы
took this Lviv from the
забрали этот Львов у
Poles to
Поляков чтобы
return it back  to
вернуть вернуть кому
Poland again, why did we take away territories from the Soviet Union
Польше ещё раз зачем мы у Советский Союз
from the Poles?
у Поляков
When Hitler attacked them, they
забирали территории Когда на них напал
took it back, they took it back, to return it. Cool,
вернуть забрали чтобы вернуть Прикольно
I’m taking your phone so that I can
я у вас забираю телефон чтобы когда-то
give it back to you someday, yes, I
вам вернуть так
understand. Cool, yes, interesting, yes,
да понял Прикольно Да интересно Да так
that is, I understand correctly, yes, what?  you
то есть я правильно понимаю Да что у вас
don’t have a single argument Why the
нет ни единого аргумента Почему
Soviet Union attacked uh Poland and I
Советский Союз напал на ээ Польшу а я
’ll say Yes because the Soviet Union as an
скажу Да потому что Советский Союз как
imperialist power together with the
империалистическая держава вместе с
Third Reich was the Union
третьим рейхом был Союз
Yes the Soviet Union raised Hitler The
Да Советский Союз врасти Гитлера
Soviet Union
Советский Союз
nurtured He helped stab in the back our
вскормила Он помог удар в спину нашим
brothers the Slavs the Poles Yes when they
братьям славянам полякам Да когда они
fought  with Hitler's Germany, the
боролись с гитлеровской Германией
Soviet Union stabbed in the back Yes, they
Советский Союз ударил в спину Да
captured
захватил
Polish prisoners of war and thus laby the
военнопленных польских да лаби этим
Polish army and gave Hitler the opportunity
польскую армию и дав возможность Гитлеру
to capture his part of Poland they call
захватить свою часть Польши называют
Please remind me that what do the
Напомни мне пожалуйста что как вас
Polish brothers call you I don’t know Ukrainians Ukrainians
братья поляки называют не знаю украинцы
Ukrainians and
украинцев украинцы а
Ukraine is not some interesting
Украин не не там какое-то интересное
expression  What Say say yes don’t
выражение Какое Скажи скажи да не
Remember And now
Вспомни А сейчас
in short some kind of something the
короче какое-то да какие-то там всё вот
Russians call it all just like this
русские называют пр просто типа вот
Dear Ukrainians Yes, look
Уважаемые украинцы Да так вот смотри ещё
again at our relationship with the Poles, we’ll
раз наши взаимоотношения с поляками мы
sort it out, we’ll need to beat their faces there, we’ll
разберёмся мы и там нужно побьём морды
need to make friends, these are ours  their
нужно подружимся это наши с ними
relationship, you still tell me smart
взаимоотношения ты всё-таки скажи умный
Tomsk
Томский
Megamind
Мегамозг
Why did the Soviet Union bring Hitler to
Зачем Советский Союз привёл Гитлера в
Eastern Europe instead of
Восточную Европу вместо того чтобы
helping Poland like England helped France
помочь Польше как помогала Англия
Yes, he
Франция Да он
hit Poland in the back Yes, giving
и ударил в спину Польши Да дав
Hitler the opportunity to seize and strengthen himself
возможность Гитлеру захватить укрепиться
Yes, and then also attack the Soviet
Да а потом ещё и напасть на Советский
Union Remind  please let me know on what
Союз Напомни мне пожалуйста по какому
occasion did Churchill express the expression that Yes,
поводу Черчиль высказал выражение что Да
you are already You are in the second circle Yes, the people
ты уже Ты по второму кругу Да пофиг чель
there hated why did Churchill even
там ненавидел по что вообще Черчиль
think about it? Yes, you are responsible for the
думал про это Да ты отвечаешь за
Soviet Union, why did he attack, what did
Советский Союз почему он напал что там
Churchill think? Yes, it doesn’t matter at all Well, he
Черчиль думал Да это вообще пофиг А ну
attacked us Yes  I don’t care at all And no I do
напал нам Да пофиг вообще А нет не пофиг
n’t care Well I just don’t care Yes because the
Вот как раз не пофиг Да потому что
Soviet Union Yes violated international
Советский Союз Да нарушил международное
law and violated the sovereignty and
право да нарушил суверенитет и
territorial integrity of Poland Yes
территориальную це целостность Польши да
And most importantly helped Hitler Yes to
И самое главное помог Гитлеру Да её
capture it, strengthen himself and then
захватить укрепиться и э дальше потом
move on to the Soviet Union, which entailed
двинуть на Советский Союз что повлекло
millions of casualties  Soviet citizens
миллионные жертвы советских граждан
Yes, I don’t care at all, I don’t
Да пофиг на вообще пофигу Вот то есть
care at all That is, you don’t care about everything, yes you don’t care about everything Yes,
вам всё пофигу да вам всё пофигу Да
millions of lives were killed through this
миллионы жизней убито через этот
Soviet Union Yes, but you don’t care about anything
Советский Союз Да но вам всё пофигу
But
доходит А вот до твоих мозгов доходит
your very same argument is reaching your brains A Yes, I don’t care, I
твой же самый аргумент А Да пофиг
understood Yeah stuck on my own  Argumen envy
понял Ага завис на своём же аргумен зави
dadada I’m just thinking damn well, really, but
дадада Я просто думаю блин ну реально а
it turns out
получается
then where is all this great Russian
тогда где этот весь великий русский
intellect Soviet education Tomsk
интеллект Советское образование Томский
State University where
государственный дебелий университет где
is it if it cannot give birth to a
это оно если оно не может родить
justification Why is this con
обоснование Почему вот это кон
state the Soviet Union attacked
государство Советский Союз напало вместе
Poland along with the Nazis and tore it
с нацистами на Польшу разорвала её на
apart  and unleashed the Second World War
части и развязала Вторую Мировую Войну
Yes,
Да пофиг
I don’t care to think Yes, I’m just laughing Okay dude,
соображать Да я просто ржу Ладно чувак
look, you and I will finish the letter
смотри мы с тобой будем заканчивать пись
on my Telegram right away, the VN
на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
axis apoc tse more and more respectfully YouTube took
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the scum of ODS in your ban and you
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people  Sometimes we don’t
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational link
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
is written directly at the same time and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okrim video is also the same Tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж е цикава и
Korisna information and we are guilty of you trimati
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independent in that we will show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Slava  Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
pipis a
пидпись а